<?xml version="1.0"  encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">  <channel>
    <title>CoderIvy.com</title>
    <link>http://sample.com</link>
    <pubDate>05 May 19 21:19 NZST</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to make the native scrollbar thinner in Google Chrome?</title>
      <link>http://sample.com/default/How-to-make-the-native-scrollbar-thinner-in-Google-Chrome%3F/</link>
      <pubDate>2019-05-04 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most people known how to add a scrollbar to your pages when the content of an element is too big to fit in the specified area. So, I will just give a brief introduction to CSS &lt;strong&gt;overflow&lt;/strong&gt; property. &lt;strong&gt;overflow&lt;/strong&gt; property has the following values:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;visible - Default. The overflow is not clipped. The content renders outside the element&amp;rsquo;s box&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;hidden - The overflow is clipped, and the rest of the content will be invisible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;scroll - The overflow is clipped, and a scrollbar is added to see the rest of the content&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;auto - Similar to scroll, but it adds scrollbars only when necessary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please &lt;strong&gt;note&lt;/strong&gt; that: the &lt;strong&gt;overflow&lt;/strong&gt; property only works for block elements with a specified height.&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First and the easiest way to set a scrollbar&amp;rsquo;s width is to use &lt;strong&gt;scrollbar-width&lt;/strong&gt; property. &lt;strong&gt;scrollbar-width&lt;/strong&gt; is a property that controls the width or &amp;ldquo;thickness&amp;rdquo; of a scrollbar. &lt;strong&gt;scrollbar-width&lt;/strong&gt; accepts the following values:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;auto is the default value and will render the standard scrollbars for the user agent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;thin will tell the user agent to use thinner scrollbars, when applicable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;none will hide the scrollbar completely, without affecting the element&amp;rsquo;s scrollability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;length&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is being debated, but (if added) would be a maximum width of the scrollbar.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More details, please visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://css-tricks.com/almanac/properties/s/scrollbar-width/&#34;&gt;css-tricks&lt;/a&gt;. Please &lt;strong&gt;note&lt;/strong&gt; that &lt;strong&gt;scrollbar-width&lt;/strong&gt; supports higher version browser.&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Following code show another way to set the scrollbar thinner in Google Chrome:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;.your-class-name {&#xA;  height: 100%; &#xA;  over-flow-y: scroll;&#xA;&#xA;  &amp;amp;::-webkit-scrollbar {&#xA;    width: 2px;&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ps: if there is any mistake, please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>